<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Stattic Docs</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site</link>
<description>Latest posts from Stattic Docs</description>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:08:50 -0000</lastBuildDate>

<item>
<title>Installation and setup guide</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/installation-and-setup/</link>
<description>This comprehensive guide covers everything you need to know about installing and setting up Stattic on different operating systems and environments. System Requirements Minimum Requirements Python: 3.8 or higher Operating...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/installation-and-setup/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Template system</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/template-system/</link>
<description>Master Stattic's powerful Jinja2 template system to create beautiful, custom designs for your static site. This guide covers everything from basic template structure to advanced customization techniques. Overview Stattic uses...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/template-system/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Quick start guide</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/quick-start/</link>
<description>Get up and running with Stattic in just a few minutes! This guide will take you from installation to your first deployed static site. What is Stattic? Stattic is a...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/quick-start/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Configuration</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/configuration/</link>
<description>Master Stattic's configuration system to customize your static site generator for your specific needs. This guide covers all configuration options, command-line flags, and best practices for different use cases. Overview...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/configuration/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Project structure</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/project-structure/</link>
<description>Understanding Stattic's project structure is crucial for organizing your content, customizing your site, and maintaining a clean, scalable website. This guide explains every file and directory in a Stattic project...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/project-structure/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Your first static site with Stattic</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/your-first-static-site/</link>
<description>This step-by-step tutorial will guide you through creating your very first static site with Stattic. By the end, you'll have a fully functional website with multiple pages, blog posts, and...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/your-first-static-site/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Content creation</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/content-creation/</link>
<description>Master the art of creating compelling content for your Stattic site. This guide covers everything from basic Markdown syntax to advanced content organization, helping you create engaging blogs, documentation, and...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/content-creation/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Deployment options</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/deployment-options/</link>
<description>Complete guide to deploying your Stattic-generated static sites across popular hosting platforms. Since Stattic generates standard HTML/CSS/JS files, you have complete freedom to choose any static hosting provider. Overview Stattic...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/deployment-options/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Front matter reference</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/front-matter-reference/</link>
<description>Complete reference guide for YAML front matter in Stattic. Front matter is the metadata that appears at the top of your Markdown files, controlling how your content is processed, displayed,...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/front-matter-reference/</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stattic CLI Reference</title>
<link>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/cli-reference/</link>
<description>Complete command-line interface reference for Stattic. This guide covers all available commands, options, and practical usage examples to help you master the Stattic CLI. Overview Stattic provides a powerful command-line...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 04:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://docs.stattic.site/blog/cli-reference/</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>